<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>poetry on green | hugo-scratch-1 | 0003</title>
    <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/tags/poetry/</link>
    <description>Recent content in poetry on green | hugo-scratch-1 | 0003</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 12:16:40 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/tags/poetry/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Trees by Joyce Kilmer</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/trees-by-joyce-kilmer/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 12:16:40 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/trees-by-joyce-kilmer/</guid>
      <description>I think that I shall never see A poem lovely as a tree. A tree whose hungry mouth is prest Against the earth’s sweet flowing breast; A tree that looks at God all day, And lifts her leafy arms to pray; A tree that may in Summer wear A nest of robins in her hair; Upon whose bosom snow has lain; Who intimately lives with rain. Poems are made by fools like me, But only God can make a tree.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>That It Will Never Come Again by Emily Dickinson</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/that-it-will-never-come-again-by-emily-dickinson/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 12:14:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/that-it-will-never-come-again-by-emily-dickinson/</guid>
      <description>That it will never come again Is what makes life so sweet. Believing what we don’t believe Does not exhilarate. That if it be, it be at best An ablative estate -- This instigates an appetite Precisely opposite. </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>If by Rudyard Kipling</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/if-by-rudyard-kipling/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Nov 2020 11:57:52 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/if-by-rudyard-kipling/</guid>
      <description>If you can keep your head when all about you Are losing theirs and blaming it on you, If you can trust yourself when all men doubt you, But make allowance for their doubting too; If you can wait and not be tired by waiting, Or being lied about, don’t deal in lies, Or being hated, don’t give way to hating, And yet don’t look too good, nor talk too wise: If you can dream—and not make dreams your master; If you can think—and not make thoughts your aim; If you can meet with Triumph and Disaster And treat those two impostors just the same; If you can bear to hear the truth you’ve spoken Twisted by knaves to make a trap for fools, Or watch the things you gave your life to, broken, And stoop and build ’em up with worn-out tools: If you can make one heap of all your winnings And risk it on one turn of pitch-and-toss, And lose, and start again at your beginnings And never breathe a word about your loss; If you can force your heart and nerve and sinew To serve your turn long after they are gone, And so hold on when there is nothing in you Except the Will which says to them: ‘Hold on!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
