<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Youtube on green | hugo-scratch-1 | 0006</title>
    <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/tags/youtube/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Youtube on green | hugo-scratch-1 | 0006</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 19:28:37 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/tags/youtube/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>0749 Green Firefox Current Tabs</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0749-green-firefox-current-tabs/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Nov 2020 19:28:37 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0749-green-firefox-current-tabs/</guid>
      <description>Record what was going on, and a chance to organise and review Note that pinned tabs have been removed.
When the markdown is pasted in, there are no line breaks so all the links run together. At the moment, the simple solution is to add an asterisk space at the front of each line.
The best way to do this with Visual Studio Code is to:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Git and Github From the Coding Train</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/hugotips/git-and-github-from-the-coding-train/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 17 Nov 2020 19:27:31 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/hugotips/git-and-github-from-the-coding-train/</guid>
      <description> The Coding Train | Git and Github for Poets | Youtube Playlist This is a very easy to watch 11 video set playlist, which led to looking for a way to get the thumbnail for the first video on the playlist. Searched for &amp;ldquo;youtube thumbnail grab&amp;rdquo; and found Get YouTube Thumbnail which returns images and links when the youtube link is entered,for large and small thumbnails. these two are shown below:  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Shortcode Youtube</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/hugotips/shortcode-youtube/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 20:13:47 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/hugotips/shortcode-youtube/</guid>
      <description>example of using an existing shortcode Medium | The Agent | shortcodes in Hugo Hugo | built in short codes
--- title: &amp;quot;Embed a Youtube video&amp;quot; date: 2020-01-01T14:17:03-05:00 draft: false ---    How to create a custom shortcode So how do we create our own custom shortcode?
It’s fairly easy. All we have to do is create a shortcodes folder under the layouts folder, and put the HTML file that we want the shortcode to insert in the folder.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0737 | Youtube Videos to Watch</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0737-youtube-videos-to-watch/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 16 Nov 2020 14:17:22 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0737-youtube-videos-to-watch/</guid>
      <description>Youtube videos on CSS, websites, data science, git, Jamstack  codeSTACKr | Learn CSS Grid in 20 minutes Antonin Januska | CSS Grids For Responsive Blog-Site Layouts CSS 1 line layouts, with youtube link Netlify Tutorial - How to build and deploy websites using Netlify Git and GitHub for Beginners - Crash Course JAMstack Course - Build websites that are simpler, faster, and more secure Geeklaunch | How to make a website and put it online 2017 tutorial (Hugo, Linux)  Other websites of interest  Hugo blog setup hugo favicon  </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0735 | Publish Hugo Website on Github</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0735-publish-hugo-website-on-github/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 14 Nov 2020 23:56:16 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0735-publish-hugo-website-on-github/</guid>
      <description>GeekLaunch has a Youtube Hugo playlist (7 videos) Youtube | GeekLaunch | How to make a website and put it online 2017 Tutorial (Hugo, Linux)
Github
youtube shortcode   Web: Sign into github account Web: Create new repository and copy the address for the git remote add origin Terminal: navigate to green websites/hugo-harrycresswell This is where some Hugo testing is in progress.
Terminal: git commands git init git remote add origin https://github.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0727 youtube-dl</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0727-youtube-dl/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 17:32:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0727-youtube-dl/</guid>
      <description>LINKS  One example of youtube-dl documentation One source for the executable  CONFIG Use Command Prompt in Windows from Downloads folder e.g. youtube-dl &amp;hellip;youtube video link&amp;hellip;
wakey05 folder has youtube-dl.conf with some config in it for mp4, best quality and date and time to actual download so it shows up in latest.
Status Individual files from youtube downloaded ok but no luck with playlists.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0726 Set up RSS feed for Youtube channel</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0726-youtube-rss-feed/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 10 Nov 2020 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0726-youtube-rss-feed/</guid>
      <description>RESULT Some youtube channels have channel, others have user&amp;hellip;
A number have been set up in the old reader.
https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?channel_id=
https://www.youtube.com/feeds/videos.xml?user=</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>0719 netlify</title>
      <link>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0719-website-deploy-to-netlify/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 31 Oct 2020 15:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://dormouseroared.github.io/hugo-scratch-1/0719-website-deploy-to-netlify/</guid>
      <description>Watch the video   Watched Brad Traversy&amp;rsquo;s Youtube video. Build a Responsive Website | HTML, CSS Grid, Flexbox &amp;amp; More
  A CSS framework like Bootstrap is not used. Instead, CSS is used in two ways. As utility classes, used as part of HTML, as per CSS frameworks, and in the usual way to target specific HTML. The CSS resulting is quite long though.
  Netlify is used to deploy to a live website, and as well as github (used previously but not this time) a project folder can be dragged in to netlify.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
